Taking his wife was their last mistake.
Redemption Day is a action, romance, war film directed by Hicham Hajji.
When his wife is kidnapped by terrorists for ransom, veteran war hero Brad Paxton races against the clock to
rescue her in a daring and deadly operation that pits him against powerful and dark forces.
Brad Paxton, played by Gary Dourdan.
Kate Paxton, played by Serinda Swan.
Ambassador Williams, played by Andy Garcia.
Younes Laalej, played by Brice Bexter.
Ed Paxton, played by Ernie Hudson.
Tom Fitzgerald, played by Martin Donovan.
Redemption Day is a 2021 American action thriller film
directed and co-written by Hicham Hajji.
The film stars Gary Dourdan, Serinda Swan, Andy García, Martin
Donovan, Robert Knepper and Samy Naceri and follows the U.S.
Marine who travels to Morocco to rescue his kidnapped wife.
It was distributed by Saban Films.
The tone is dark and emotional.